For all of you who say, Amanda, you explain too much.
Let me explain one more thing for you.
I like explaining.
I explain everything else.
Why wouldn't I explain myself on my own terms when I feel like it?
There's just far too much on this internet of telling folks about what type of person
they need to be to appease whatever standard each of us has for what a person should be.
Now, if we're talking about like genocide or racism or harm, okay.
If you feel that I explain too much, you can keep that to yourself because I promise you
there is something that I think you do too much.
And unfortunately, I don't get the chance to say it to you.
So let's just keep it even.